### Sean Klein

(267)-756-3870 seanrk06@icloud.com

### Skills

Skilled in project management, data analytics, and team leadership. I also possess knowledge of a multitude of programming languages, including but not limited to Python, C, and Javascript. With those languages I have accumulated experience and am now able to build full-stack web applications using multiple frameworks within the aforementioned languages.

# **Experience**

June 2019 - August 2019

#### **Southampton Day Camp** - Counselor In Training

• Helped supervise a group of kids for a Summer under the leadership of a head counselor.

June 2021 - August 2021

#### **Taco Bell** - Service Champion

- Worked as a cashier for both the drive-through and front register.
- Oversaw customers' meals from the kitchen in order to make sure they received their complete order

June 2021 - August 2021

### **Neurological Practice**- Research Assistant

- Managed data relating to patient records in research involving migraine patients.
- Oversaw patient-facing facilities and made sure equipment was maintained properly.
- Cataloged medication for study subjects.

June 2022 - August 2022

#### **Restaurant** - Busser

 Addressed service-related needs of the customers in addition to team support of coworkers.

### **Education**

Date of Graduation: 2024

#### High School -

- 4.2 Weighted GPA
- Business Courses:
  - Accelerated Personal Finance
  - o Introduction to Entrepreneurship
- AP Courses
  - AP United States History
    - Received a 5 on the National AP Test
  - o AP English Lang
  - AP Psychology
  - o AP European History
  - AP Computer Science Principles
- In School Extracurriculars
  - Technology Club
    - Co-president as of August 2022
    - The goal of this club is to increase student understanding of modern technology through discussion groups, demonstrations, and hands-on experiences.
  - NASA Hunch Club
    - Co-leader as of August 2022
    - Co-leader of a team of 14 students whose goal is to produce a working
      Insect Nano Containment Box prototype to be potentially used on the ISS
  - o Amatuer Radio Club
    - Leader as of August 2022
    - Marketing team leader on a team of 6 whose job is to reach out to national news organizations for coverage of our schools ARISS program. News stations contacted include but are not limited to ABC National, Fox, NBC, CBS, Bucks County Herald, and Philly Magazine and Inquire
  - Model United Nations
    - Represented Argentina on the Economics and Finance Committee at national competition
  - Roe Kappa Social Studies Honors Society
    - Inducted on Oct. 2022
  - Jewish Heritage Society
  - Computer Science Club
  - o Future Business Leaders of America (FBLA)

### **Awards**

- Received two honorable mention awards for my project Refuge For Ukraine which can be found here <a href="https://devpost.com/software/refuge-for-ukraine">https://devpost.com/software/refuge-for-ukraine</a>
- Received business student of the month for exemplary work (May 2022)
- Inducted into Roe Kappa honors society

## **Outside of School Extracurriculars**

- STEM Enrichment of Pennsylvania (stempa.com)
  - Co-president and founder
    - The STEM Enrichment of Pennsylvania or STEME is an organization run independently by students driven to improve youth literacy in STEM through partnerships with local businesses and communities.
- Sigma Alpha Rho fraternity
  - President of Phi Chapter as of Jan. 2021
  - Sigma Alpha Roe is a student-run youth organization that has had thousands of alumni over its 100 year history. The primary goal is to instill a sense of leadership and values in young men.
  - o In my time as president, I more than doubled the size of our group from 8 to 20 and we plan to continue to expand.
- Volunteering
  - I have committed over 50 hours to the Wrightstown Farmers Market, a local market that supports healthy soil, produce, pastures, animals, people, and local communities.
- Martial Arts
  - I have learned and studied Tang Soo Do for the last 9 years of my life. During which I have achieved a Second Degree Black Belt as of 2020.
  - I have been awarded many distinctions such as a Gold medal in the 2017 Pilsung Martial Arts Association Championship
- Programming
  - Website Development
    - Personal Portfolio Website (<a href="https://seanklein.info/">https://seanklein.info/</a>)
      - I built this website to display my achievements and my recent projects to act as a "virtual resume."
    - Technology Club Website (<a href="https://technologyclub.netlify.app/">https://technologyclub.netlify.app/</a>)
      - This website serves to explain what my club is about to new or incoming students
    - RefugeForUkraine Website
      - (https://devpost.com/software/refuge-for-ukraine)
        - This award-winning website was designed to track the Russia-Ukraine War visually to send help where it's most needed.

■ ForgetMeNot Website

(https://devpost.com/software/forget-me-not-93xuw2)

- Teachers and students alike have struggled with virtual learning since the start of the pandemic. This website can help with the productivity of students and the management of teachers.
- Study Buddy Website (<a href="https://devpost.com/software/study-buddy-rit0sq">https://devpost.com/software/study-buddy-rit0sq</a>)
  - The Covid-19 pandemic has increased anxiety globally. Study Buddy was made to help young adults cope with social anxiety. It is not hosted live.